Take your chance. Make your move.
Feel the Beat is a comedy, music, drama film directed by Elissa Down.
After failing to make it on Broadway, April returns to her hometown and reluctantly
begins training a misfit group of young dancers for a competition.
April, played by Sofia Carson.
Nick, played by Wolfgang Novogratz.
Barb, played by Donna Lynne Champlin.
Frank, played by Enrico Colantoni.
Coach Buzz, played by Dennis Andres.
Wellington 'Welly' Wong, played by Rex Lee.
Feel the Beat is a 2020 American family dance comedy drama film directed by Elissa Down, written by Michael
Armbruster and Shawn Ku and starring Sofia Carson, Enrico Colantoni and Wolfgang Novogratz.
The film was released on Netflix on June 19, 2020.
It received mixed reviews.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.